What do you think you're doing?
You looked cold, so I thought I'd be an extra blanket for you.
Since I'm your familiar.
No, thanks!
It's been like this ever since she came here.
She's always glued to me at home.
Give me some space to be a man.
Right, I have to take back control!
I'll teach her who's boss once and for all!
The first step is to uncover her weakness
Now then
There's really no point in wearing clothes inside, you know
What the heck is wrong with her?
I'm so much more comfortable without anything on
I suppose some might call that a shortcoming
What is it, Chota Baby?
This is for you
Your master commands it
Put some clothes on
So awkward
Is it over yet?
I put it on for you
Thank you so much for the thoughtful present
Crap, it didn't work
I wonder how she'll respond to a little bitterness
You're so sweet
Guess I'm the only one who thinks it's gross
What about our neighbor's scary dog?
Mom, I'm the only one who finds something to fight
If I want to be the greatest mage one day
I have to have ultimate control over my familiar
I'm sorry
You want to know Luco has weaknesses?
Yeah
Oh, I know, I've got something good
Tell me, tell me
Those flesh orbs slow her down
It's way too hard to dodge attacks with those things
I don't think I've got weaknesses
Okay, then, I'd say it's liquor
Liquor?
I thought she prided herself on how well she could hold her liquor
Well, of course she can
But that's not what I mean
I'm saying she won't resist any alcohol that's put in front of her
She's usually overly cautious about everything
Except when it comes to throwing them back
You could poison a drink and she'd chug it down
I'm not trying to kill her!
You're asking about weaknesses
But from any dragon's perspective
Humans are nothing but weaknesses
Even if you manage to find something
Do you really think it would be enough to keep Lucoa at bay?
I thought the two of you were doing well
No, we're not
I'm not
Lucoa's always wandering around somewhere without telling me
If she's here, she's teasing me
Or making fun of me
She just doesn't respect me at all
I want to find some kind of weakness of hers
So she'll remember I'm the one in charge
I'm pretty sure she knows that already in her own way
Lucoa's one of those dragons that can't stay in one place for very long
If she's still with you, it's because she likes you
Shout to sweetie
There you are
How long have you been here?
Actually, I just arrived
I want to go home
Wait, I'll escort you
See you later
You know, kid
I would have told you my weakness if you had just asked
The thought that truly terrifies me the most is having my home taken away
I once made a huge mistake, you know?
And I was driven out of my homeland
It really broke me down
Ever since then, I've been afraid of settling in one place
One day, a friend who I thought would never have a home found one for herself somehow
I admit, I admit, it made me kind of jealous
And that's why you came to me
But why me?
Because you're the one who invited me in
You're the first one to ask me to stay
I can't tell you how happy it made me to hear that
Yeah, but I asked you as a familiar
Honestly, I know I'm not a good match
You're incredible at what you do
And I'm not nearly experienced enough yet
That's true
I'm a phenomenal familiar
Which is why I could read you at first glance
You're a good boy with a kind heart who works hard
Even to the point of overextending yourself
Seeing that was good enough for me
Thank you
Such a cutie
Whatever
I really wish she'd stop treating me like a helpless infant
All yours, Jota
Let me know whenever you want it, okay?
What do you mean by that?
Wow, what's wrong?
That was quite the dramatic sigh
Well, my parents are coming to visit me
Oh
What are you going to do about Fafnir?
Hmm
I asked if he'd like to go adventuring in the mountains or something while they're here, but
I absolutely refuse
Apparently there's a brand new hardcore video game releasing at the same time, so
I guess you'll just have to introduce them
Right
Both of my parents are pretty forward
So the thought of them upsetting Fafnir and watching my treasures get half destroyed is just
You're worried about your weeb collection?
I refuse
I can't afford to move from this spot
Not until I've gathered all trophies
You're pretty invested
I mean, you've already beaten the game
Why not reward yourself with a little time off?
Dragons can fight off their enemies for thousands of years
You don't need to worry about me
Another bust
Well, that's that
What do I do now?
Hmm
Hang on
Really?
You're having trouble getting Fafnir to listen to you?
Yeah, I figured you might have some pointers since you've known him the longest
Perhaps
I suppose I do owe you for planning that hot springs trip for us
Thank you, Toru
So what would you suggest that I try?
Use Brick Fars!
Give him no choice but to obey your commands!
Force is your only way in!
With Fafnir?
Use Force?
You know that's impossible, right?
Not really
It's the only method I've ever used with him
When we first met, he attacked me for trying to sleep in his cavern and we battled
Not bad
You're quite skilled as well
Once we recognized each other's strength, he finally decided to share space in his big cave with me
Wow, pretty intense for a first meeting
I realize that method might be a bit much for a human to take on right away
Maybe ask Lukawa?
You really think she can help?
Okay, what's her number?
Hana, knock it off!
And she hung up on me
Who do I know who knows Lukawa?
Oh!
I added Shota to my friends list the last time we played games together
What? You're here for Lukawa?
She said she was going abroad for fun
She's not around
Dang it
Wait, do you need help with something?
If so, I'd be happy to assist if I can
You mean that?
Yup
I'm constantly working to improve my skills as a mage every single day
Helping others would serve as a part of my training
Oh wow, you're a very responsible young lad
Here's the sitch
That's impossible!
You're, uh, talking about that scary dragon?
Yeah, I guess that's what he is
I'm thinking it might be easier to do something about my parents than Fafkun
Huh? Who's Fafkun? The dragon?
I thought his name was Fafnir
Is Fafkun his nickname or something?
What? Hmm, yeah, it is
He's accepted that nickname as a special gift from you?
I don't know about that, but he's fine with it
Then you can form a pact
What do you mean?
If you've given him a special name, and he's accepted it
Then the preparations to form a pact are nearly complete
Take this
What is it?
An orb of magic power
I've poured my own magical powers into it
That should be enough for someone who doesn't have abilities to use it
You should at least be able to activate the ritual to forge a pact
Really?
You're incredible, Shota
Well, um, maybe not
Would it be okay to ask you for a favor in return?
Oh, sure
Like some life force?
Only devils ask for that
I was hoping I could convince you to exchange a lesson or two for my services
I wanna be a cool adult too
What?
That's a pretty ambitious request, kid
I'm not right for the job
I don't know anything about being cool
So it's a promise then
We're making a pact
Huh
I'm home
A master-servant pact
Wow
Fafkun
Hmm?
This is for you
What?
An orb of magic power?
You think this'll do the trick?
Oh
I'm still not leaving
Fine, it's a bust then
Riddle me this, Fafkun
How is it that someone as prideful as you
Was able to accept a nickname from me?
I had no idea you were taking a risk with that
I see
Hm, I suggest you be grateful to whichever brat gave you that measly orb
He gave it to me in exchange for some advice on being a suave adult
An adult? Huh
What do you think the term adult means to a dragon?
Um, well, it means they've matured out of their immature state
It does not
That only refers to the physical state of the body
There is no concept of adult or child in a dragon's mind
We can only track our growth in life by strength
Our state of mind is dependent upon that
Parents don't protect their offspring
Dragons never used terms like adult or child until more and more of us started interacting with humans
Do you understand? Takya?
Takya?
It means dragons are living their lives like humans
They know such values will lead to nothing but foolishness
But abide by them anyway
The dragons here act the same
We're all masquerading as humans
Okay, I can tell you don't really believe that
I hear it in your voice
Yes
I do
Toru has firmly declared she will never regret her reckless decisions
And that human, Kobayashi, drove away the Emperor of Demise
I grew curious as to why they would go so far to keep up the act
So I decided to try playing the human game myself to learn a bit more
That's the only reason I'd let you give me a nickname
At long last it dropped
This is fantastic news
Takya, I'm in a good mood now so if you can defeat me I'll play along with your family visitors or whoever they are
Yeah?
I could never defeat you with strength though
Who said it had to be physical?
There's no way I'm gonna lose this
You dare to challenge me, human?
You'll never defeat me no matter how hard you try
Hey, no fair, you can't use insta-kill combos
We humans have no choice, we'll use any means necessary
You assume I'm cool enough to teach you something based on my neat outwardly appearance
That means being a cool guy starts with creating your own individual look
Just the other day, I went as far as where the rivers meet by myself
I guess if that's true then you are worthy of praise my friend
It's so true, I have pictures to prove it
Oh nice, that's a really cool photo
I know, it's incredible
Stop that
Whatever, Hachiska
Even caterpillars go there by themselves
What are you saying?
Think you can make it there too?
Of course I can
Fine, go there by yourself
And bring back pictures is proof
Like the easiest challenge ever
Now what do I do?
I'm so dumb, why'd I have to say that?
We can do it together
But we're gonna have to walk a long way to get to where the rivers meet
Go team, we can do this
Thanks, Kana!
Hey!
Kana, here's some lunch and tea
Brought you some candy from the dagashi shop
Thanks, Ilulu
And thanks, Lady Toru
You have fun, okay?
Mm-hmm
Saikawa!
Hi, Kana!
Doesn't this feel kind of grown up heading out somewhere by ourselves?
George, you let me borrow this
She said to contact her if anything happens
And now we're all set to take photos as proof too
Scamp, scamp, love, love, scamp
Let's only step on the white parts
K
If you fall, you're dead
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ah!
Eh!
Aah!
And now, OOP!
No-Ah!
I'm immortal!
Not fair!
It's two!
It's not!
Aah!
Asaikawa, you die.
Nuh-uh! I'm immortal!
Not fair!
It's too!
It's not!
Yes, it is!
Kana! Watch this!
Yes!
Saikawa!
Oh!
Uh...
Ah!
One, two, three!
Wow, your lunch looks so beautiful and delicious!
Lady Toru made it for me.
Yours looks good, too, Saikawa.
Oh, thank you!
Georgie's very good at cooking!
Thank you for our food!
Ah! I dropped it!
Will you help me, Kana?
Would you mind if I shared your chopsticks?
You can use these.
They're my spare ones.
Thank you so much!
I'll take good care of them!
Ugh!
I can use this!
Nice one, Georgie!
Thank you!
Hey, Kana!
Want some of my potato straws?
Yes, please!
Take a...
Oh!
You're apart from...
Umm-
...
Oh!
Psycho, uh, want some rolled omelets?
No. My heart is so full.
Too bad. I ate some of it already,
but it's still really yummy.
You ate some?!
Um...
Indirect kiss!
There are all kinds of people here.
I wonder why everyone's at the river.
I love rivers so much.
It feels good to bathe in the water.
You do what?!
Connor bathes in the water!
Connor!
Oh!
Connor's such an angel!
This feels so good!
Lady Alma, you forgot your perception blocking.
Oh, no!
Wait! I need photo evidence!
Ah!
Connor, you're in the way! Move!
Oh, so cute!
I can't right now!
Huh?!
Wait! Where'd it go?!
Look, Connor! We did it!
We made it to where they said they meet!
Yeah!
We need to get a photo for proof!
Hmm!
Like me to take it for you?
Uh-uh!
Uh...
If you can, thanks!
Sure!
Okay!
Here we go!
Yay!
That's a cute pose, Connor!
Thank you very much!
Where did you two come from?
From a Borosuka!
My!
That's quite a walk, isn't it?
Yeah, but it's been fun! We got to see where the rivers meet!
Oh?
Well, you know, they've only met at this spot since they changed the flow of the river!
Oh!
Why did they change it?
They believed it would prevent floods from happening and that it would be easier to grow rice!
Later!
Be careful now!
Kay!
What's the matter?
You okay?
Do you think I'm gonna change, too?
Okay!
No!
That is uncomfortable.
They will change too?
Well of course you will!
You'll keep getting cuter and cuter!
I'm looking forward to it!
And are you going to change?
Oh yeah!
Obviously nope day I'm going to be a fierce woman!
I'm telling you the truth!
We saw a monster in the river!
No way something like that exists, can you tell us what it was like?
Huge! It was this big and bathing in the river, right, Connor?
Psycho Eye, that was a CG.
Are you sure?
So it was like an AR or something?
I told you it was gonna be fake.
That's good.
For real though?
Wasn't it neat?
Hi, Ms. Kobayashi. Good afternoon.
What's going on, Shota?
Did it happen? Am I cool yet?
Takya, what did you do?
This is me, Bond. Who's rotten?
Taurus.